我都不觉得自己是一名厨师
that I had a culinary identity.
在餐馆开业前
Before the restaurant opened,
我想象出所有的
I dreamed up of all the
我在餐馆中期待能吃到的东西
things that I would like to eat at a restaurant.
对虾丝配西瓜姜糖
泰式鸡炖汤,拌鸡丝,鲜蟹,　　香菇,酢酱草与甜椰子
海鲂,布朗黄油,芦笋,墨鱼仔,西班牙辣香肠
泰国菜 欧洲菜 大师的菜
Thai dishes, European dishes, dishes from mentors.
熏鲑鱼汤,猪油渣和现熏罗勒籽
血肠佐煎鹌鹑蛋,五行草奶油蛋卷
成型辣脆皮羊肩,欧洲防风根,　　　　　　小银甜菜,黑加仑,松仁和单克丽奶酪
泰式炒咖喱,猪腩,长杠豆
三份猪肉 速度
Three pork, away!
三份?
Three?
三份猪肉 一份鸡肉 是在做这些吧?
Three pork, one chicken, is that what we're doing?
是的
Yes.
我们手忙脚乱地准备菜品
And we were running around, trying to cook this food,
却完全不明白自己在做什么
had no idea what we were doing.
取菜 取菜 主厨
Picking up. Pick up, Chef.